http://www.vetquip.com.au/privacy-policy/

No products in the quote list. HomeRepairs & ReturnsProductsOur BrandsEquipmentAnaesthesiaAutoclavesDentalDiagnostic / ConsumablesElectrocauteryIV Fluid TherapyMilaLightingMonitoringOrthopaedicOrthopaedic – Bone PinsOrthopaedic InstrumentsOrthopaedic Plates & ScrewsOrthopaedics – ConsumablesOrthopaedics – TTAInstrumentsSurgical InstrumentsForcepsScissorsNeedle HoldersCatalogueContact UsService & MaintenanceTestimonialsAbout Us Privacy PolicyVet Quip Pty Ltd (ABN: 19 101 880 899) and its related companies (together VetQuip, we, us, our and other similar expressions) are committed to protecting your personal privacy.
This Privacy Policy tells you how we collect, store, use and disclose your personal information.
We encourage you to read this policy carefully so that you understand our information handling practicesInformation we collectIn order to provide our customers with our products and services, we may collect and use personal information about you and others. If we are not provided with all the personal information we request, we may not be able to supply our products and services.The type of information we collect includes names, addresses, credit card details (if you buy products or services from us) and other contact details.We do not normally collect or store ‘sensitive information’, as defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (eg. information about ethnic origin, religious beliefs or health). However, if we do, we will only collect that information with your consent or as otherwise permitted by law.Collection of Credit InformationIf you are a customer and we give you credit, we may also collect credit information or credit eligibility information about you. Credit information and credit eligibility information are particular types of personal information.The credit information and credit eligibility information we may collect about you includes: identification information; credit liability information; repayment history information; details of any request for your information that we receive from a credit provider, mortgage insurer or trade insurer; the type and the amount of credit sought; default information; payment information; court proceedings information; personal insolvency information; information about any serious credit infringement by you; information disclosed in reports obtained from credit reporting bodies; information from property searches; and information provided by trade references.We generally collect your credit information or credit eligibility information directly from you, for example, if you complete our Commercial Account Application Form.We may also collect credit information or credit eligibility information about you from third parties.
For example, from any organisation with whom you have any dealings, credit reporting bodies such as Veda, or from publicly maintained records.The purpose for which we may collect, hold, use and disclose credit information or credit eligibility information about you, is so we can assess whether to extend credit to you or to a customer (if you have given a personal guarantee in respect of that customer).If permitted under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), we may disclose credit information or credit eligibility information about you to any organisation with whom you have any dealings, credit reporting bodies, creditors, other traders in the markets we trade in, our commercial customers, our suppliers and  retailers of our products.How we collect personal informationGenerally, we collect an individual’s personal information from that individual. For example, we may collect information from you when you complete our Commercial Account Application Form, or provide a personal guarantee, or when you provide us with information, whether in person, by telephone, online or in writing. If you submit an order (including by telephone or online), we will collect information necessary to fulfil that order.However, occasionally we may also collect personal information from someone other than the individual, for example from any other organisation with which you have had any dealings, or which you have nominated to act as trade referee, or from publicly maintained records.How we store personal informationWe take all reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information which we hold about you and to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorised alteration. Any personal information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Access to personal information is limited to those of our personnel who specifically need it to carry out their business responsibilities. We also maintain physical security procedures to manage and protect the use and storage of records containing personal information.We are not responsible or liable for the security of data sent via the internet.Purpose of collectionWe collect personal information so we can:Use & disclosureWe use and disclose the personal information we collect for the purposes indicated above, and for other secondary purposes.We usually disclose the personal information we collect to our related entities, service providers and contractors, who help us supply our products and services. For example, we may disclose the personal information we collect to our information technology providers, providers of marketing and promotional services, professional advisors such as legal practitioners and accountants, debt collectors and insurers.Except where indicated above, we will not use or disclose your personal information to a third party unless:MarketingWe may use your personal information to advise you of new products and marketing initiatives that we think may be of interest to you. This may include product and service offerings, newsletters and general information about us.If you prefer not to receive information about our products and services you can ask to be removed from the relevant circulation list by contacting us, using the details listed below.We never disclose personal information to a third party for the purpose of allowing them to direct market their products or service to you, unless you have expressly consented to that disclosure.AccessIf at any time you want to know what personal information we hold about you, you are welcome to request access to that information by contacting us, using the details listed below. We may charge a fee to cover the reasonable costs we incur in processing your request.We may also choose to deny your request for access where:If we deny your request for access, we will let you know why.Quality & correctionAt all times we strive to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If at any time you believe the personal information that we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, you should let us know. We will use all reasonable efforts to correct the information.Website & cookiesTo ensure we are meeting the needs and wants of our website users, and to develop our online services, we may collect aggregated information by using cookies or similar electronic tools.Cookies are small amounts of information sent from a web server to your computer.
These cookies are used to retain login and location information in order to make your experience more convenient and personal.
We do not use cookies to track your internet activity before or after you leave our website.
No other business has access to our cookies.We do not use this technology to access any personal information of a user in our records and a user cannot be personally identified from a cookie.Changes to our Privacy PolicyAs our business evolves our business processes and policies will be reviewed and may be revised. We may change our Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you of any change by posting an updated version of our Privacy Policy on our website. Please check our website regularly.ComplaintsWe are committed to constantly improving our procedures so that personal information is treated appropriately. If you feel that we have failed to deal with your personal information in accordance with this policy or in accordance with the Australian Privacy Principles, please contact us, using the details listed below, so we have an opportunity to resolve the issue to your satisfaction.We will log your complaint and our privacy officer will:If we have tried to resolve your complaint and you are not happy with our response, you may also contact the Office of Australian Information Commissioner by calling 1300 363 992 or by visiting www.oaic.gov.au.Disclosure to overseas recipientsWe are not likely to disclose your personal information to recipients located overseas.Contact usIf you require more detailed information about our information handling practices or if you have any concerns about our handling of your personal information, you can contact VetQuip’s Privacy Officer via our email form.We will endeavour to respond to your concerns as quickly as possible. VetQuip Catalogue DownloadWith a comprehensive line of products, from a range of leading manufacturers, it is no wonder that veterinarians trust VetQuip for the very best products and equipment for their practices.Download CatalogueProfessional, friendly and helpful staff, are always available todiscuss your requirements and to provide answers to your technical questions.Full Name*Practice/Company*Email*
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms. We value privacy and would never spam you. Need Help? Call Us TodayIf you are looking for a specialty item, specific piece of equipment or a hard to find item. Or if you are interested in learning more about the products we have on offer, or would like to learn more about how to use a particular product, let one of our skilled staff members help you find what you are looking for.Call 1300-888-427About VetQuipVetquip offers an extensive range of products and services to meet the specialised needs of veterinarians, universities, research facilities and zoos.Head Office: NSW Branch21-25 Interchange Drive, Eastern Creek.
NSW
2766Phone: 1300-888-427 Direct: 02 9899 6666 Email: sales@vetquip.com.auPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Collection Notice © 2019 VetQuip Pty Ltd - A Covetrus Company
COVID-19 Update: If you are returning a product, please observe some basic rules to help keep our team safe. Read more Dismiss
